(Beverly:)is difficult to ignore.
AMY:
I know how you feel.
(Amy:)She didn't invite any of us.
It was spur of the moment!
(Bernadette:)But we did get to see a live
stream of it on the Internet.
(Beverly:)I could've watched it
on the Internet?
(Amy:)Thank you.
(Penny:)So if we would have asked you
to come to Vegas
(Penny:)to see us get married,
you would've come?
(Beverly:)No, I would've said
you're making a huge mistake.
(Beverly:)But an invitation
would've been nice.
(Penny:)You really think
we made a mistake?
(Beverly:)At the time I did.
But I-I've never seen
Leonard so happy,
(Beverly:)so... perhaps I was wrong.
(Penny:)Wow.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Penny:)Well, um, how about this?
(Penny:)Maybe while
you're still in town,
(Penny:)Leonard and I could have
another small ceremony.
(Penny:)You know, if you're interested.
(Beverly:)I would find that
perfectly acceptable.
(gasps) She would find it
perfectly acceptable!
You guys saw it! We bonded!
(Bernadette:)Howie?
(Bernadette:)You doing okay?
You've been in there a while.
WOLOWITZ: (stammers)
I'm fine. Be right out.
(Howard(through bathroom door):)Am I an American hero?
(chuckles)
(Sheldon:)Well, that's
a good question, Jim.
(Howard(through bathroom door):)Don't you think once
an astronaut leaves the planet,
(Howard(through bathroom door):)he's a hero to all the nations
of the Earth?
(toilet flushes)
(Howard(through bathroom door):)Okey dokey.
(Howard(through bathroom door):)I think I have time
for one more question.